Command his family here with the number
seven overall pick in the 2026 draft.
Sunny Styles in the building here.
Looking good in that burgundy and gold
hat, my brother. First things first.
Congratulations.
>> Yeah, I appreciate it. I'm blessed. I
just want to give all the glory to God,
man. Super excited. Can't wait to get to
Washington and get to work.
>> Amen. Amen. And you were overcome with
emotion when you found out about that
pick, man. What hit you in that moment
because you knew you were going at some
point tonight, but that emotion still
hit, man. What was that about?
>> Man, you know, I had a lot of great
visits. Um, you know, but when I was in
that building, it was different. Coach
Noran was different. Coach Jones was
different. Coach Quinn, Mr. Peters,
every meeting just felt different. It
felt right. Felt like they had amazing
people in the building all the way to
like the player development staff.
Everybody was just great people. Um, so
I'm super excited to come to that
building. And
>> and you must have been excited cuz even
the crew, you brought Richie rocking the
burgundy suit. So there's a little bit
of vibes there that maybe you were going
to come to the burgundy and gold. Did
you know that you would be coming here
at number seven?
>> I told my family this morning I was
going to be a commander pick seven. They
there told me a bunch of other teams. I
was like, I'm telling you, I know what
it is. I had a gut feeling. So, I'm just
I'm excited it happened. It's the
perfect fit.
>> And you said during your visit, you told
DQ, I hope I'm back here soon. What
about Washington made it the perfect fit
for you,
>> man? Um, I think it's the people that
that's what drew me to Ohio State. You
know, obviously when you're getting
recruited out of college, I mean, out of
high school, you have to pick where you
go. And, uh, the people is what drew me
to Ohio State. And then with the
commanders, it was the people. Um, Coach
Quinn, Mr. Peters, a great man. Coach
Jones a great man. Coach Doran's another
great man. Like everyone I met, like I
said in the building were great people,
great men and women. Um, so that's
really what drew me there. You know, I
think I'm a I'd like to say I'm a good
person and uh I like to surround myself
by other good people. So I'm glad I get
to come into that building.
>> And a lot was made about your
versatility about you being a former
safety, which is wild to think that you
can run a 4-3 being this massive. What
is that versatility and that experience
in multiple positions? Why does that
make you the most dangerous person in
this 2026 NFL draft? Yeah, I think when
you are versatile and can do a multitude
of roles for a defense, it makes the
defense unpredictable, especially as a
coordinator. You have a bunch of
different chess pieces on the board, uh,
it makes you makes you unpredictable,
like I said. Um, you know, I think I can
do a lot of things. And I think the, you
know, the best part about me, I'm just
scratching the surface. Um, you know,
I'm super excited where I'm at right
now, but there's still so much work to
go.
>> And last, but not least, you get to
share this moment with your brother. He
is here at the draft with you, man. How
special is this, not only for you, but
for your family who also sacrificed so
much for you to get to this point? And
me and him been working for this since
we was 5 years old. Um, and I told my
dad, I was like, "Hey, dad, you gonna
cry today." He was like, "Man, I was up
early in the morning, too." He's like,
"This ain't no surprise." Um, so I think
that perspective of it, like, it's no
surprise being here, but, you know,
obviously super blessed and appreciated
to be here.
>> And Sunny, we're going to let you
celebrate cuz we know this is a big
moment for you. We know your brother's
still out there. Last thing, Commanders
fans are all excited to have you here.
Give a message to the fans on what they
can expect to see when Sunny Styles on
the field this year.
>> Man, you're getting a guard loves the
game. uh gonna be fast, violent,
physical, and uh get better each and
every week and just help the team win.
>> Amen to that. We love winning, baby.
Commanders family here with our number
seven pick at Ohio State, Sunny Styles.
Congratulations, brother.
>> Yes, sir.